[
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Work : Leisure"
            },
            {
                "option": "Day : night"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Expedite : Procrastinate"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "frequently : Always"
            }, 
            {
                "option" : "Happy : Unhappy"    
            }
        ],
        "answer":"none",
        "tag" : "gi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "March"
            },
            {
                "option": "January"
            },
            {               
                "option": "August"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "june"
            },
            {
                "option" : "May"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"june",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "BY"
            },
            {
                "option": "LO"
            },
            {               
                "option": "EW"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "GT"
            },
            {
                "option":"SH"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"EW",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "25-5"
            },
            {
                "option": "16-4"
            },
            {               
                "option": "144-12"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "64-7"
            },
            {
                "option":"36-6"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"64-7",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "28"
            },
            {
                "option": "42"
            },
            {               
                "option": "21"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "65"
            },
            {
                "option":"35"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"65",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "25-E"
            },
            {
                "option": "16-D"
            },
            {               
                "option": "144-L"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "64-G"
            },
            {
                "option":"36-F"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"64-G",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Driver, passener, vehicle"
            },
            {
                "option": "Chair, table, bench"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Ship, Boat, Pilot"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Apple, Orange, Winter"
            },
            {
                "option":"Mango, flower, orchard"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Chair, table, benchh",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Door"
            },
            {
                "option": "Gate"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Table"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Window"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Table",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "CIRE"
            },
            {
                "option": "NAIR"
            },
            {               
                "option": "LOUDSC"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "RNUTHDE"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"CIRE",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "NMLK"
            },
            {
                "option": "RQPO"
            },
            {               
                "option": "UTSR"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "WXUV"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"WXUV",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "WRONG"
            },
            {
                "option": "GREEN"
            },
            {               
                "option": "WHITE"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "RIGHT"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"GREEN",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Bird"
            },
            {
                "option": "Insect"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Aeroplane"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Kite"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Insect",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Salt"
            },
            {
                "option": "Black pepper"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Chilli"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Coriander"
            },
            {
                "option": "Jira"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Salt",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Table"
            },
            {
                "option": "Chair"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Cupboard"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Bed"
            },
            {
                "option": "Computer"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Computer",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Apple"
            },
            {
                "option": "Papaya"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Litchi"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Guava"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Litchi",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
    ,
    {
        "question": "Select the odd one_",
        "options":[
            {
                "option": "Kitten"
            },
            {
                "option": "Goat"
            },
            {               
                "option": "Calf"
            },                  
            {
                "option": "Foal"
            },
            {
                "option": "Lamb"
            }
        ],
        "answer":"Goat",
        "tag" : "gi"
    }
]